[
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The letter ‘a‘ is a _________.",
        "correct_answer": "vowel",
        "incorrect_answers": ["consonant"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Does she _____ a brother?",
        "correct_answer": "have",
        "incorrect_answers": ["has"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "That car is _______.",
        "correct_answer": "mine",
        "incorrect_answers": ["me", "my", "I"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "I _____ a new car.",
        "correct_answer": "bought",
        "incorrect_answers": ["buy"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The letter ‘d‘ is a _________.",
        "correct_answer": "consonant",
        "incorrect_answers": ["vowel"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The letter ‘e‘ is a _________.",
        "correct_answer": "vowel",
        "incorrect_answers": ["consonant"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "They ____ _____ happy.",
        "correct_answer": "are not",
        "incorrect_answers": ["am not", "is not", "is not"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "She ____ a brother.",
        "correct_answer": "has",
        "incorrect_answers": ["have", "is", "the"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The food is ____ the table.",
        "correct_answer": "on",
        "incorrect_answers": ["under", "of", "in"]
    },
    {
        "category": "English",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "____ they have money?",
        "correct_answer": "Do",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Does", "Are", "Is"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for telephone",
        "correct_answer": "el teléfono",
        "incorrect_answers": ["un paraguas", "un teléfono", "el agua"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How do you say Good Morning?",
        "correct_answer": "Buenas tardes",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Adios", "Buenos días", "Buenas noches"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘Spanish’?",
        "correct_answer": "Español",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Inglés", "Portugués", "Italiano"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How do you say Good Afternoon?",
        "correct_answer": "Buenas tardes",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Buenos días", "Buenas noches", "Adios"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘Good Night’?",
        "correct_answer": "Buenas noches",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Buenos días", "Buenas tardes", "Adios"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for Please?",
        "correct_answer": "Por favor",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Por favor", "Por favor", "Por favor"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘Thank You’?",
        "correct_answer": "Gracias",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Adios", "Derecha", "Perdon"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘Hello’?",
        "correct_answer": "Hola",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Adios", "Buenos días", "Buenas noches"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘Goodbye’?",
        "correct_answer": "Adios",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Hola", "Buenos días", "Buenas noches"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘Yes’?",
        "correct_answer": "Sí",
        "incorrect_answers": ["No", "Sí", "Sí"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘No’?",
        "correct_answer": "No",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sí", "No", "No"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘I’?",
        "correct_answer": "Yo",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Yo", "Yo", "Yo"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘You’?",
        "correct_answer": "Tú",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Tú", "Tú", "Tú"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Spanish",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for the word ‘We’?",
        "correct_answer": "Nosotros",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Nosotros", "Nosotros"]
    }
]
